让我们一头扎进去，建立这个尼格罗尼球迷的网站，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Let's dive in and
and build this Negroni fan site, right?
我真的很兴奋。
I'm really excited about this one.
内格罗尼是我最喜欢的饮料。
Negroni's my favorite drink.
所以它们很有趣。
So they're a lot of fun.
我觉得建这个网站也会很有趣。
And I think building the site
is also gonna be a lot of fun.
所以让我们关上这些窗户，进入内格罗尼遗址。
So let's close up these windows and
get into the Negroni site.
所以，在我们的 Negroni 网站，我们会注意到一些事情。
So, in our Negroni site,
we're gonna notice a couple things.
首先，我们有一个. 环境文件。
So first out of the gate,
we have a .environment file.
所以我们要学习一些关于环境变量的高级知识。
So we're gonna get into some advanced
stuff with environment variables.
而且我们也是从零开始。
And also we're kind of
starting from scratch here.
所以我们得到的历史只是一些文本。
So we've got the history
is just some text.
索引只是以文本形式存在。
The index is just in text.
没有布局组件。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: There
is no layout components.
所以这是我的一个拼写错误。
So that's a typo on my part.
原谅我。
Forgive me.
我们有了索引文件和历史文件,
So we've got our index file and
our history file,
我们只是用碎片包裹起来。
which we're just wrapping in fragments.
我们得到了一些我们现在没有使用的图像
We've got some images that
we're not using right now and
然后我们有一些内容，我们现在没有使用。
then we've got some content
that we're not using right now.
让我们来看看我们的起点是什么。
So let's just take a look at what
this where our starting point is.
我们将开发纱线工作空间网格。
We'll do yarn workspace negronis develop.
现在我们已经建好了这个网站。
So now we've got this site built.
如果我回到我们的主页,
And if I go back to our homepage,
我们有一个简单的主页，一点点文本
we have kind of a simple homepage,
a little bit of text and
然后通过一个链接来学习一些历史，一段轻松的历史。
then a link through to learn some history,
a light history.
但还是没有内容。
But again there's no content.
这不是一个，杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 我们需要这个
This is not a,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: We need this
做很多事，对吗？
to do a lot, right?
所以我们需要安装一些主题。
So we need to install some themes.
我们将做纱线工作空间 negronis 添加，和
We'll do yarn workspace negronis add, and
我们要添加 gatsby-plugin-theme-ui,
we're gonna add gatsby-plugin-theme-ui,
这需要和主题 ui 一起来。
and that needs to come
along with theme-ui.
它还需要带有@emotion / core 和@mdx js / react。
It also needs to come along with
@emotion/core and @mdx=js/react.
因为我不想写出整个对象,
And then because I don't wanna
have to write that whole object,
我只是要包括一些@theme-ui / preset。
I'm just gonna include
some @theme-ui/presets.
这样我们就可以从一个主题开始，而不用自己去选择一个正确的主题。
So that we can start with a theme
without having a right one ourselves.
在我们的配置文件中,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: In our config
file to actually use this,
让我们设置模块，导出，然后我们设置插件。
let's set up modules.exports and
we will set up plugins.
我们只用 gatsby-plugin-theme-ui。
We're just gonna use
gatsby-plugin-theme-ui.
演讲者2: 这是专家的模块吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is this supposed
to be module the experts?
詹森 · 兰斯托夫: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Yes, it is.
这将是我今天的死期。
That is gonna be the death of me today.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
所以我们有 module.exports，然后我们有了我们的插件数组。
So we've got module.exports and
then we've got our plugins array.
首先，我们将使用 gatsby-plugin-theme-ui。
And to start we're just gonna
use gatsby-plugin-theme-ui.
然后我想设置一个主题。
I then want to set up a theme.
所以让我们进入这里，我们将做 gatsby-plugin-theme-ui 和
So let's go in here,
we'll do gatsby-plugin-theme-ui and
我们要做一个索引文件来覆盖主题。
we're gonna do an index
file to override the theme.
然后我要导入机器人主题。
And then I'm gonna
import the roboto theme.
我要把它作为主题输入，这样我们就不必在下面重命名它了。
I'm gonna input it as theme so
that we don't have to rename it below.
我们将从主题-ui / 预设中导入它。
And we're gonna import that
from the theme-ui/presets.
然后我可以 export.default 和
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And
then I can export.default and
把主题放进去。
just kinda drop the theme right in there.